sunnylanelive.com 2019-10-26

# VNA Privacy Policy

  * bobbiedenlive.com
  * charleechaselive.com
  * evalinlive.com
  * gabbyquinteros.com
  * shandafay.com
  * tealconrad.com
  * foxxedup.com
  * nataliastarr.com
  * womenbyjuliaann.com
  * wydesydeproductions.com
  * alexlegend.com
  * allanalallthetime.com
  * angelinacastrolive.com
  * blownbyrone.com
  * carmenvalentina.com
  * cristiannlive.com
  * deauxmalive.com
  * fuckedfeet.com
  * itscleolive.com
  * jelenajensen.com
  * juliaannlive.com
  * kimberleelive.com
  * kink305.com
  * maxinex.com/
  * maggiegreenlive.com
  * nikkibenz.com
  * ninakayy.com
  * pennypaxlive.com
  * pumaSwedeXXX.com
  * samanthagrace.net
  * rachelstormsxxx.com
  * kendrajames.com
  * romemajor.com
  * rubberdoll.net
  * sarajay.com
  * siripornstar.com
  * sophiedeelive.com
  * sunnylanelive.com
  * vnatasha.com
  * vickyathome.com
  * sexmywife.com
  * POVMania.com
  * girlgirlmania.com

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to THE SITES and governs data collection and usage. THE SITES are not an ecommerce site. All commerce takes place on the billing company servers. We do not store or ask for any personal or credit card information on our sites. By using any of THE SITES, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.  

Collection of your Personal Information We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information (username and password) to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) signing upfor special offers from selected third parties; (c) sending us an email message; To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. 

Sharing Information with Third Parties THE SITES do not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. 

  THE SITES may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to THE SITES, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

  **WE DO NOT SHARE EMAIL ADDRESSES OR CONTACT DATA WITH THIRD PARTIES FOR MARKETING PURPOSES, WHATSOEVER.**

THE SITES may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on THE SITES or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of THE SITES; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of THE SITES, or the public. 

  Automatically Collected Information Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by THE SITES. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of THE SITES. 

  Use of Cookies THE SITES may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

  One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize THE SITES pages, or register with THE SITES or services, a cookie helps THE SITES to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to one of THE SITES where the cookie was previously created, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the THE SITES features that you customized. 

  You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of THE SITES services or websites you visit. 

  Security of your Personal Information THE SITES secures your personal information (username and password) from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. THE SITES uses the following methods for this purpose: 

   \- SSL Protocol 

  We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed. 

External Data Storage Sites We may store your data (user/pass) on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted. 

Changes to this Statement THE SITES reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy. 

  Contact Information THE SITES welcome your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that THE SITES has not adhered to this Statement, please contact THE SITES by clicking the support link at the bottom of the page: 

  THE SITES  

  Effective as of January 01, 2003
